Tisch Library Records UA137
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tisch Library Records
1960 -- 1990
1853 -- 2017
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Wessell Library
Tisch Library
Lilly Music Library
UA137
77.75 Linear Feet
1 Volumes
117 Digital Object(s)
91.3 Megabytes Of the 117 digital objects, 92 digital objects comprise 91.3 megabytes.
This collection contains materials pertaining to the Tisch Library, the libraries that preceded Tisch as the Arts and Sciences library, and related branches of the Tufts University libraries.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list. This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by Tisch Library, 2006 -- 2021.
Arrangement
The collection is organized into twelve series: Artifacts; Exhibits and events; Annual reports; Committee files; Buildings and plans; Correspondence; Subject Files; Undergraduate Research Award; Unprocessed accessions; 2019 accessions; 2020 accessions; and 2021 accessions.
Biographical / Historical
The Tisch Library (1860-present) opened in 1996 as the main Arts, Sciences, and Engineering library at Tufts University, made possible by a generous donation from the Tisch family. Between 1965 and 1996, the Arts and Sciences library was known as the Wessell Library. From 1908-1965, the library was known as the Eaton Library and was housed in Eaton Hall.
Prior to the 1860-1861 school year, the library began as the personal collection of President Hosea Ballou. In 1860, that collection was moved to Ballou Hall as a permanent library space for students to have easier access to the material. In 1886, the library moved to Middle Hall (later called Packard Hall) (Light on the Hill, 74). In 1906, Andrew Carnegie donated $100,000 to build the Eaton Library, in its own space. The Eaton Library, completed in 1908, was named after Crane Theological School graduate Rev. Charles H. Eaton, who was the Carnegie family pastor who graduated in 1874 (Light on the Hill, 201).
In 1965, the entire collection of the Eaton Library moved into a brand-new building, the Wessell Library, named for Tufts University President Nils Y. Wessell. The collection comprised of Crane Theological School materials temporarily moved into the Wessell Library in the mid-1960s, but the materials were transferred to the Harvard Divinity School in 1973 after the Crane Theological School closed in 1968.
The Wessell Library, which then became the main library for Arts, Sciences, and Engineering (the latter department moved its collection to Wessell Library in 1990 from the Lufkin Engineering Library). In 1996, the name of the library was changed to the Tisch Library after a donation from the Tisch family (Jonathan Tisch is an alumnus and is on the Board of Trustees). The library currently houses the collection for the Arts, Sciences, and Engineering departments.
Custodial History
The materials in this collection were originally multiple collections, the Tufts Libraries collection and the Tisch Library records. The provenance of the earlier materials is largely unknown; these materials were processed as the Tufts Libraries collection, but during the course of processing the Tisch Library materials it was decided to incorporate the Tufts Libraries collection into the Tisch Library records. In addition, the materials relating to the Ginn Library were removed from this collection and became the Ginn Library records (UA198). Materials which were in an obvious original order were maintained in that order, but the materials from the Tufts Libraries collection were not in their original order at the start of this project.
Related Materials
Ginn Library records, 1931 -- 2010. Tufts University. Digital Collections and Archives. Medford, MA.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains materials pertaining to the Tisch Library, the libraries that preceded Tisch as the Arts and Sciences library, and related branches of the Tufts University libraries. The materials consist of artifacts, event posters, notes, meeting minutes, correspondence, reports, slides, publications, photographs, and author talk videos. The bulk of this material was created between 1960 and 1990. These records were created by librarians and other staff at the Tisch Library and other Tufts University libraries. This collection includes a complete collection of annual reports dating from 1862 to 1995. In addition, this collection contains a great deal of material created by former librarian Murray Martin and his predecessor Joseph Komidar.
University history; Academic Support -- Libraries, Galleries, Archives; Teaching and learning; Facilities; Curriculum and Instruction -- Scholarships, Fellowships, Awards
- Artifacts, 1856 -- 2010; UA137.001; 1.95 Linear Feet; 1 Volumes
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains artifacts relating to the Tisch (formerly Wessell) Library.
  Arrangement
  This series is organized roughly chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Rules, 1860; UA137.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Bookplates, 1877 -- 1956; UA137.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Gift Bookplate Original, 1926; UA137.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Copper Plate, library acknowledgement of gift from Taber Ashton Fund, 1900 -- 1925; UA137.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Copper Plate, Tufts College Library acknowledgements, 1870 -- 1880; UA137.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Bookplate and Original Plate, 1870 -- 1950; UA137.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - "W" from Wessell Library, 1964 -- 1965; UA137.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Signed Mug, 1996; UA137.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Hard Hat, 1996; UA137.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Tisch Library Construction Paper Weight, 1996; UA137.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Libraries Promotional Pencils, 2006; UA137.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Golden Book of Names from Eaton Library, 1952; UA137.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Circulation Book, 1856 -- 1860; UA137.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Circulation Book, 1860 -- 1877; UA137.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Tisch Library Rooftop Garden Model, 2007; UA137.001.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Purple and grey handled mug, 2000 -- 2003; UA137.001.032.00001 (Box 32)
  - Black handled mug, 2004 -- 2006; UA137.001.032.00002 (Box 32)
  - White and blue mug, 2007 -- 2010; UA137.001.032.00003 (Box 32)
  - Picture frame, 2000 -- 2010; UA137.001.032.00004 (Box 32)
- Exhibits and Events, 1995 -- 2013; 2005 -- 2012; UA137.002; 6.5 Linear Feet; 1 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains materials relating to exhibits and events held at the Tisch Library.
  This series is arranged chronologically by exhibit/event date.
  - 5,000 Years of Recorded Human History, 1995 -- 2000; UA137.002.005.00001 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Lincoln Forever Free Exhibit, 2005; UA137.002.005.00002 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Lincoln Forever Free Exhibit, 2005; UA137.002.005.00003 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Lincoln Forever Free Exhibit, 2005; UA137.002.005.00004 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Lincoln Forever Free Exhibit, 2005; UA137.002.005.00005 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Lincoln Forever Free Exhibit, 2005; UA137.002.005.00006 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Lincoln Forever Free Exhibit, 2005; UA137.002.005.00007 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Lincoln Forever Free Exhibit, 2005; UA137.002.005.00008 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Lincoln Forever Free Exhibit, 2005; UA137.002.005.00009 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Lincoln Forever Free Exhibit - Indiana Boyhood, 2005; UA137.002.005.00010 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Lincoln Forever Free Exhibit - Abigal Al-Doory's Records, 2005; UA137.002.005.00012 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Lincoln Forever Free Exhibit - Abigal Al-Doory's Records, 2005; UA137.002.005.00013 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Lincoln Forever Free Exhibit - Abigal Al-Doory's Records, 2005; UA137.002.005.00014 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Lincoln Forever Free Exhibit - Abigal Al-Doory's Records, 2005; UA137.002.005.00015 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Lincoln Forever Free Exhibit - Abigal Al-Doory's Records, 2005; UA137.002.005.00016 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Lincoln Forever Free Exhibit - Abigal Al-Doory's Records, 2005; UA137.002.005.00017 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Lincoln Forever Free Exhibit - Abigal Al-Doory's Records, 2005; UA137.002.005.00018 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Lincoln Forever Free Exhibit - Abigal Al-Doory's Records, 2005; UA137.002.005.00019 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Lincoln Forever Free Exhibit - Abigal Al-Doory's Records, 2005; UA137.002.005.00020 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - John Holmes exhibit opening, 1999-09-17; UA137.002.005.00021; Sloan, J. D., 1946-
    Opening celebration of the John Holmes exhibit.
    Michalak, Jo-Ann; Sauer, Anne; DiBiaggio, John A.; Eyges, Doris Holmes; Duke, Winslow; Colati, Greg; Stanton, Paul
  - 5,000 Years of Recorded Human History, 1995 -- 2000; UA137.002.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - Lincoln Forever Free Exhibit, 2005; UA137.002.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - READ Posters - Faculty, 2008; UA137.002.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - Library Week and READ, 2009; UA137.002.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - Sam Cornish - 5th John Holmes Memorial Poetry Reading Exhibit, 2009; UA137.002.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - Beyond September 11, 2009; UA137.002.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - Frank Ackerman, 2009; UA137.002.007.00001 (Box 7)
  - Library Roof, 2009; UA137.002.007.00002 (Box 7)
  - Fit for Freedom, 2009; UA137.002.007.00003 (Box 7)
  - READ - Teams, 2010; UA137.002.007.00004 (Box 7)
    Jumbo was played by Tony Kodzis.
  - Lobby Exhibit Materials, 2010; UA137.002.007.00005 (Box 7)
  - Summer Reading, 2010; UA137.002.007.00006 (Box 7)
  - World Peace Foundation, 2010; UA137.002.007.00007 (Box 7)
  - Lincoln Exhibit Posters and Post Hanging, 2005 -- 2009; UA137.002.008.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 5)
    This oversized folder contains posters for the following exhibits and events: Frank Ackerman, Communities Thrive @ Tisch Library, Beyond September 11, Edward R. Murrow Papers, V-12 @ Tufts, John Holmes Collection, Lincoln Forever Free Exhibit, and National Library Week 2009.
  - Honored faculty, Honored books [1 of 2], 2010; UA137.002.030.00001 (Box 30)
  - Honored faculty, Honored books [2 of 2], 2010; UA137.002.030.00002 (Box 30)
  - International Mirth [1 of 4], 2002 -- 2010; UA137.002.030.00003 (Box 30)
    Exhibit by Harriet Chenkin and Julia Metzidakis.
  - International Mirth [2 of 4], 2002 -- 2010; UA137.002.030.00004 (Box 30)
  - International Mirth [3 of 4], 2002 -- 2010; UA137.002.030.00005 (Box 30)
  - International Mirth [4 of 4], 2002 -- 2010; UA137.002.030.00006 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 4)
    In map case. Exhibit by Harriet Chenkin and Julia Metzidakis.
  - Holmes Memorial Reading: Robert Pinsky [1 of 3], 2003 -- 2011; UA137.002.030.00007 (Box 30)
  - Holmes Memorial Reading: Robert Pinsky [2 of 3], 2003 -- 2011; UA137.002.030.00008 (Box 30)
  - Holmes Memorial Reading: Robert Pinsky [3 of 3], 2003 -- 2011; UA137.002.030.00009 (Box Shared 2)
    Oversized box.
  - Kareem Roustom exhibit [1 of 2], 2010; UA137.002.030.00010 (Box 30)
    Created by Sophia Cacciola.
  - Tufts Black History exhibit [1 of 2], 2002 -- 2010; UA137.002.030.00011 (Box 30)
    Created by students Kristen Johnson, Ashley Asiedu-Frimpong, and Kyle Halle-Erby. Contains some original photos.
  - Tufts Black History exhibit [2 of 2], 2002 -- 2010; UA137.002.030.00012 (Box 30)
    Created by students Kristen Johnson, Ashley Asiedu-Frimpong, and Kyle Halle-Erby.
  - David M. Carroll exhibit [1 of 2], 2010; UA137.002.030.00013 (Box 30)
    Exhibit team: Harriet Chenkin, Anthony Mengelkamp, and Regina Raboin.
  - David M. Carroll exhibit [2 of 2], 2010; UA137.002.030.00014 (Box 30)
  - Barbara Grossman exhibit, 2001 -- 2010; UA137.002.030.00015 (Box 30)
    'A Spectacle of Suffering: Clara Morris on the American Stage.' Exhibit team: Harriet Chenkin, Anthony Mengelkamp, and Regina Raboin.
  - Christoph Borgers exhibit, 2011; UA137.002.030.00016 (Box 30)
    Exhibit team: Anthony Mengelkamp and Regina Raboin.
  - Judith Nies exhibit, 2011; UA137.002.030.00017 (Box 30)
  - Brian Brenner exhibit, 2011; UA137.002.030.00018 (Box 30)
  - Frank Bidart exhibit, 2012; UA137.002.030.00019 (Box 30)
    Spring 2012
  - War of 1812 exhibit, 2012; UA137.002.030.00020 (Box 30)
    Winter 2012; in conjunction with Hugh Howard author talk.
  - Lilly Music Library Ritter Collection exhibit, 2013; UA137.002.030.00021 (Box 30)
  - Tufts Libraries' One Millionth Book exhibit, 2000; UA137.001141 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Transferred by Tisch Library, September 2022, UA-2023-019.
    Four exhibit placards describing the Tufts Libraries' One Millionth Book Celebration.
- Annual Reports, 1862 -- 1995; UA137.003; 2.9 Linear Feet
  This series contains the annual reports of the Tisch Library. These reports were created annually from 1862 to 1995. The series is complete, missing only the 1929 and 1982 annual reports. These reports were created by the University Librarians of those years: A.A. Keen (1862-1866), William R. Shipman (1866-1868), Helen L. Mellen (1868-1907), Ethel Hayes (1907-1928), Raymond L. Walkley (1928-1955), Dorothy Union (interim 1955-1956), Joseph S. Komidar (1956-1981), Murray S. Martin (1981-1989), John E. Austin (1989), and David McDonald (1989-1995).
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  - Annual Reports, 1862; UA137.003.005.00021 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1863; UA137.003.005.00022 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1864; UA137.003.005.00023 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1865; UA137.003.005.00024 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1866; UA137.003.005.00025 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1867; UA137.003.005.00026 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1868; UA137.003.005.00027 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1869; UA137.003.005.00028 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1870; UA137.003.005.00029 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1871; UA137.003.005.00030 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1872; UA137.003.005.00031 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1873; UA137.003.005.00032 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1874; UA137.003.005.00033 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1875; UA137.003.005.00034 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1876; UA137.003.005.00035 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1877; UA137.003.005.00036 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1878; UA137.003.005.00037 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1879; UA137.003.005.00038 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1880; UA137.003.005.00039 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1881; UA137.003.005.00040 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1882; UA137.003.005.00041 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1883; UA137.003.005.00042 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1884; UA137.003.005.00043 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1885; UA137.003.005.00044 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1886; UA137.003.005.00045 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1887; UA137.003.005.00046 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1888; UA137.003.005.00047 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1889; UA137.003.005.00048 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1890; UA137.003.005.00049 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1891; UA137.003.005.00050 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1892; UA137.003.005.00051 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1893; UA137.003.005.00052 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1894; UA137.003.005.00053 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1895; UA137.003.005.00054 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1896; UA137.003.005.00055 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1897; UA137.003.005.00056 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1898; UA137.003.005.00057 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1899; UA137.003.005.00058 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1900; UA137.003.005.00059 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1901; UA137.003.005.00060 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1902; UA137.003.005.00061 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1903; UA137.003.005.00062 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1904; UA137.003.005.00063 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1905; UA137.003.005.00064 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1906; UA137.003.005.00065 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1907; UA137.003.005.00066 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1908; UA137.003.005.00067 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1909; UA137.003.005.00068 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1910; UA137.003.005.00069 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1911; UA137.003.005.00070 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1912; UA137.003.005.00071 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1913; UA137.003.005.00072 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1914; UA137.003.005.00073 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1915; UA137.003.005.00074 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1916; UA137.003.005.00075 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1917; UA137.003.005.00076 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1918; UA137.003.005.00077 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1919; UA137.003.005.00078 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1920; UA137.003.005.00079 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1921; UA137.003.005.00080 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1922; UA137.003.005.00081 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1923; UA137.003.005.00082 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1924; UA137.003.005.00083 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1925; UA137.003.005.00084 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1926; UA137.003.005.00085 (Box UA137 Shared 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1927; UA137.003.009.00001 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1928; UA137.003.009.00002 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1929; UA137.003.009.00003 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1930; UA137.003.009.00004 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1931; UA137.003.009.00005 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1932; UA137.003.009.00006 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1933; UA137.003.009.00007 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1934; UA137.003.009.00008 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1935; UA137.003.009.00009 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1936; UA137.003.009.00010 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1937; UA137.003.009.00011 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1938; UA137.003.009.00012 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1940; UA137.003.009.00013 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1941; UA137.003.009.00014 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1942; UA137.003.009.00015 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1943; UA137.003.009.00016 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1944; UA137.003.009.00017 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1945; UA137.003.009.00018 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1946; UA137.003.009.00019 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1947; UA137.003.009.00020 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1948; UA137.003.009.00021 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1949; UA137.003.009.00022 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1950; UA137.003.009.00023 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1951; UA137.003.009.00024 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1952; UA137.003.009.00025 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1953; UA137.003.009.00026 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1954; UA137.003.009.00027 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1955; UA137.003.009.00028 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1956; UA137.003.009.00029 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1957; UA137.003.009.00030 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1958; UA137.003.009.00031 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1959; UA137.003.009.00032 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1960; UA137.003.009.00033 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1961; UA137.003.009.00034 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1962; UA137.003.009.00035 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1963; UA137.003.009.00036 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1964; UA137.003.009.00037 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1965; UA137.003.009.00038 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1966; UA137.003.009.00039 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1967; UA137.003.009.00040 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1968; UA137.003.009.00041 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1969; UA137.003.009.00042 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1970; UA137.003.009.00043 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1971; UA137.003.009.00044 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1972; UA137.003.009.00045 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1973; UA137.003.009.00046 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1974; UA137.003.009.00047 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1975; UA137.003.009.00048 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1976; UA137.003.010.00001 (Box 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1977; UA137.003.010.00002 (Box 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1978; UA137.003.010.00003 (Box 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1979; UA137.003.010.00004 (Box 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1980; UA137.003.010.00005 (Box 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1981; UA137.003.010.00006 (Box 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1983; UA137.003.010.00007 (Box 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1984; UA137.003.010.00008 (Box 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1985; UA137.003.010.00009 (Box 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1986; UA137.003.010.00010 (Box 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1987; UA137.003.010.00011 (Box 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1988; UA137.003.010.00012 (Box 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1989; UA137.003.010.00013 (Box 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1990; UA137.003.010.00014 (Box 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1991; UA137.003.010.00015 (Box 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1992; UA137.003.010.00016 (Box 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1993; UA137.003.010.00017 (Box 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1994; UA137.003.010.00018 (Box 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1995; UA137.003.010.00019 (Box 10)
- Committee Files, 1908 -- 2006; 1965 -- 1995; UA137.004; 6.5 Linear Feet
  This series contains records for committees associated with the Tufts University libraries. Many of the committees are pan-library, but some are specific to Tisch Library. In addition, the second half of this series is committee files created by Michael Rogan, the Director of the Lilly Music Library.
  This series is arranged into two runs. The first is alphabetical by committee. The second consists of Michael Rogan's committee files, and is arranged in their original order.
  20 years from date of creation. Open for research.
  - Arts Committee, 1976 -- 1981; UA137.004.011.00001 (Box 11)
  - Arts and Sciences Library Committee, 1958 -- 1969; UA137.004.011.00002 (Box 11)
  - Board of Visitors, Annual Report, 1976; UA137.004.011.00003 (Box 11)
  - Board of Visitors, Correspondence, 1959 -- 1961; UA137.004.011.00004 (Box 11)
  - Board of Visitors, Correspondence, 1967 -- 1968; UA137.004.011.00005 (Box 11)
  - Board of Visitors, Correspondence, 1969 -- 1970; UA137.004.011.00006 (Box 11)
  - Board of Visitors, Correspondence, 1971 -- 1972; UA137.004.011.00007 (Box 11)
  - Board of Visitors, Correspondence, 1973 -- 1976; UA137.004.011.00008 (Box 11)
  - Board of Visitors, Library Policy, 1975; UA137.004.011.00009 (Box 11)
  - Board of Visitors, Memos, 1969 -- 1971; UA137.004.011.00010 (Box 11)
  - Board of Visitors, Minutes, 1959 -- 1969; UA137.004.011.00011 (Box 11)
  - Board of Visitors, Minutes, 1970 -- 1976; UA137.004.011.00012 (Box 11)
  - Board of Visitors, Organization, 1970 -- 1974; UA137.004.011.00013 (Box 11)
  - Board of Visitors, Supporting Data, 1974 -- 1977; UA137.004.011.00014 (Box 11)
  - Board of Visitors, Supporting Data, 1962 -- 1968; UA137.004.011.00015 (Box 11)
  - Cataloging Department Meetings, 1990 -- 1992; UA137.004.011.00016 (Box 11)
  - Committee on the Status of Librarians, 1983; UA137.004.011.00017 (Box 11)
  - Committee on the Status of Librarians, 1984 -- 1985; UA137.004.011.00018 (Box 11)
  - Feedback Group, 1992; UA137.004.011.00019 (Box 11)
  - Government Publications Committee, 1990; UA137.004.011.00020 (Box 11)
  - Health Sciences Learning Resources Committee, 1971 -- 1981; UA137.004.011.00021 (Box 11)
  - Librarians Assembly, 1990 -- 1993; UA137.004.011.00022 (Box 11)
  - Library Committee, 1908 -- 1954; UA137.004.012.00001 (Box 12)
  - Library Committee, 1957 -- 1967; UA137.004.012.00002 (Box 12)
  - Library Committee, 1970 -- 1980; UA137.004.012.00003 (Box 12)
  - Library Committee, 1982 -- 1985; UA137.004.012.00004 (Box 12)